BRYAN BHOOP

1266 Sweetbirch Court Mississauga, ON, L5C3R3 Bryanbhoop@gmail.com

Cell: (647) 608-6777 Home: (905) 275-3252

SUMMARY

Highly skilled IT professional with demonstrated experience in computer hardware and troubleshooting. Well versed in current industry standards within business and consumer computing. Exemplary computer literacy including statistical software, networking, and maintenance. Maintains financial records with complete accuracy and experienced with business account management, including expenses, earnings, and taxes.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Liberal Arts – Information Technology York University

January 2016- Present Toronto, ON

Management Specialist Courses University of Toronto September 2013- August 2015 Mississauga, ON

Ontario Secondary School Diploma The Woodlands School September 2007 – June 2013 Mississauga, ON

WORK HISTORY

Apartment Manager 1903035 Ontario Ltd.

November 2014 - Present Etobicoke, ON

- Manages a database of tenant contracts, Tribunal Ontario forms and invoices
- Maintains financial records for commercial real-estate
- Installs and maintains video surveillance equipment throughout the property
- Responsible for business related purchases and associated record keeping
- Completes associated contracts and legal documents for the Landlord and Tenant Board
- In charge of monthly banking and bookkeeping
- Conducts regular maintenance including painting, mending drywall and drop ceilings

Installer Impact December 2015 - Present Oakville, ON

- Wires electrical systems, ensuring structural integrity of technological devices
- Connects audio and visual systems for displays and audio mixer
- Works in a team to deconstruct large displays and arrange equipment and materials
- Constructs infrastructure including: truss stands, overhead banners, and backdrops
- Creates invoices and expense reports for accounting purposes
- Deconstructs displays, organizes equipment, and safely loads and offloads trailers
- Maintains financial records of purchases related to supply accruement

BRYAN BHOOP

1266 Sweetbirch Court Mississauga, ON, L5C3R3

Bryanbhoop@gmail.com

Home: (905) 275-3252

Cell: (647) 608-6777

Display and Booth Prep Juiceworks

October 2018 – October 2019 Mississauga, ON

- Set up digital media, visual and audio systems including laptops and smart devices on site
- Managed invoices, inventory and logistics for future reference and use
- Assisted in planning infrastructure including: trusses, backdrops, overhead banners, and rooms
- Safely ran cables carrying power and information and ensured safe unobstructed management
- Built large scale displays and booths meant for tradeshows and exhibitions
- Safely loaded and offloaded trailers including irregular sized pallets and materials

Warehouse Associate The Nuance Group

February 2013- August 2014 Mississauga, ON

- Worked cooperatively in a team on warehouse maintenance, data input, and logistics
- Meticulously sorted and encoded merchandise into a logistics computer program
- Documented, filed, and faxed paperwork to Canadian Customs (Genco)
- Managed a space designated for outgoing product processing destined for the airport
- Picked high valued items using an RF scanner following a systematic warehouse layout
- Loaded and received shipments flowing through the warehouse throughout the workday

VOLUNTEER HISTORY

CFRE Radio Host Erindale College Radio Station

December 2014 – May 2015 Mississauga, ON

- Receiving technical training on industry standard music and sound equipment
- Hosts hour long shows featuring myself as a DJ called "House Rules"
- Collaborates on group events for promotions and charity

Student Festival Manager/ Drama Club Executive Sears Ontario Drama Festival

November 2011- June 2012 Mississauga, ON

- Represented The Woodlands as stage manager of their nominated play at Sears Festival
- Compiled stage specifications and accounted for possible malfunctions
- Liaison between Drama Club and Reel Canada executives, faculty and other schools
- Organized Drama club meeting and events of 80 to 100 students
- Master of Ceremonies for Reel Canada, introducing executives, guest speakers and films

Fundraiser Heart and Stroke Foundation

August 2009- September 2009 Mississauga, ON

- Fundraised for the Heart and Stroke Foundation
- Approached people to promote Heart Month in a professional manner
- Handled personal and financial information ensuring complete confidentiality